<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">MoviesApp</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_search">Search</string>
    <string name="title_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="avatar_name">Avatar</string>
    <string name="avatar_description">A paraplegic Marine dispatched to the moon Pandora on a unique mission becomes torn between following his orders and protecting the world he feels is his home.</string>

    <string name="watch_later">Watch Later</string>

    <string name="baby_driver">Baby Driver</string>
    <string name="baby_driver_description">After being coerced into working for a crime boss, a young getaway driver finds himself taking part in a heist doomed to fail.</string>

    <string name="deadpool">DEADPOOL</string>
    <string name="deadpool_description">A wisecracking mercenary gets experimented on and becomes immortal but ugly, and sets out to track down the man who ruined his looks.</string>

    <string name="matrix">Matrix</string>
    <string name="matrix_description">When a beautiful stranger leads computer hacker Neo to a forbidding underworld, he discovers the shocking truth—the life he knows is the elaborate deception of an evil cyber-intelligence.</string>

    <string name="main_hero">Free Guy</string>'
    <string name="main_hero_description">A bank teller discovers that hes actually an NPC inside a brutal, open world video game.</string>

    <string name="world_heart">Serdtse mira</string>
    <string name="world_heart_description">Egor is a vet at a training facility for hunting dogs in a remote region of the country. Surrounded by foxes, deer, badgers, and dogs, he lives in a small building next to the house of the facilitys master. He treats the dogs, cleans the kennels, oversees the workers, and meets with clients and their dogs. Its easier for him to get along with dogs than with people. Egor is willing to take on any job to get closer to the facilitys master and his near and dear. He wants the impossible - to become a member of that family.</string>


</resources>